I am a UX Designer who has spent the last 7 years working in various capacities in research and writing. My background working for small businesses provides me with the experience of managing mid-stage business development, while my practical understanding of front-end development allows me to operate concurrently with developers in agile or lean frameworks to effectively execute design sprints.

Skills

UX Skills:

A/B Testing, Ethnographic/User Research, C&C Analysis, Card Sorting, Contextual Inquiry, E-Commerce, Heuristic Evaluation, Information Architecture, Journey Mapping, Personas, SWOT Analysis, User Scenarios, Wireframes

UI Skills:

Branding, Logo/Icon Design, Modular Design, Prototyping, Sketching, User-Centered Design, Web & Mobile Design (Adaptive & Responsive Web)

Tools:

Adobe CC (XD, Illustrator, PhotoShop), Figma, Invision, Marvel, MS Office, Shopify, Sketch, Zeplin

Projects

Spark (a subsidiary of OPSkins)

Researcher | UX/UI Designer | Branding | Logo Design | Information Architect

OPSkins is an online marketplace currently selling visual assets ("skins") for guns in various shooter games; they want to also create an online marketplace to sell AR models for use in education. Our team of 3 UX/UI Designers created a web-based prototype of a user interface which allows users to quickly create engaging augmented reality (AR) presentations. A mobile companion app is planned.

- Conducted C&C Analyses of 3D model providers and educational AR applications for mobile and web as well as a SWOT Analysis of OPSkins to identify company strengths that could be leveraged in areas where there are market gaps.
- Synthesized research data and created a feature prioritization, user personas, and navigation schema.
- Created a paper prototype to conduct usability tests to validate initial assumptions.
- Created a new subsidiary for OPSkins called 'Spark' and rebranded in order to distance the new educational AR brand from its shooter origins.
 - Created a mood board and logo, reviewed various type faces, and researched color theory alongside the psychological impact of color to determine a colorway which will encourage learning and excitement.
- Created a high-fidelity prototype to showcase a web-based user interface that is easy-to-use, familiar, and allows users to create AR-presentations from anywhere with an internet connection.



Professional Experience

Jobs for Hope (a Hack for LA project)

Jul. 2018 - Present

UX/UI Designer | Logo Design | Front-End Development

'Jobs for Hope' is an open source civic project which seeks to revamp the Los Angeles County Homeless Initiative's 'Jobs' section. The goal is to streamline the usability and search experience of skilled individuals seeking jobs that directly assist the homeless community in Los Angeles.

- Worked alongside developers to determine build limitations and execution strategies in preparation for 2-week design sprint.
- Manually scraped current 'Jobs' section for region-specific job entries to identify category trends and notable inconsistencies/redundancies between different organizations' job listings.
- Conducted usability tests of current site to identify user pain points when searching for a job as a 'Manager' and synthesizing test results with other UX researchers to inform feature prioritization.
- Created a high-fidelity wireframe and prototype to be presented to a director of the Los Angeles County Homeless Initiative to receive clearance to move forward with the project and development.
- Conducted a design studio to design a hexagonal badge/sticker to represent the Jobs for Hope project in the 2018 National Day of Civic Hacking.

Sacro & Walker LLP Jun. 2016 – May 2018

Paralegal, Commercial Litigation | Billing Coordinator | Office Administrator

Sacro & Walker is a woman and minority-owned law firm specialized in commercial litigation as outside counsel for Fortune 500 clients with their complex litigation cases.

- Assisted handling attorney(s) with legal research and document review.
 - Utilized online research tools including WestLaw, LexisNexis, and Rutter Guide.
 - Reviewed and provided edits to coverage position letters and agreed-to-litigation-plans (ATLPs).
- Prepared and drafted discovery responses pursuant to firm position and strategies.
- Organized and managed policies and claim files from multiple parties in complex litigation cases.
- Created and managed Excel documents for over 15 complex litigation cases, tracking the case statuses of all named parties in connection with case management and strategy.
- Trained new staff with firm procedures, management systems, and billing portals.

Education

General Assembly, Downtown Los Angeles

Jun. 2018 – Aug. 2018

Certificate of Completion in UX Design, Research, Strategy

University of California, Los Angeles

Sep. 2013 - Jun. 2016

Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology, Specialization in Sociocultural Studies

Pasadena City College

Jun. 2007 - Jun. 2013

Associate of Arts in Social Sciences, Specialization in Anthropology Associate of Sciences in Paralegal Studies, Specialization in Legal Research